Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
In order to restore Asta's arms, which were rendered useless after the battle with Veto, Noelle and Finral went to visit a certain group of exiles.
We'd like to talk.
Sure. I was just getting out of the bath, so...
Not what the naked thing! You're a grown man with your clothes on!
A former Diamond Kingdom commander named Fonzel Kruger, his fiancée, Dominante Code, magic items artisan,
and Mariela, who was once an assassin.
Do you have any ideas? We have to find a way to heal Asta's arms. Anything will be helpful.
So... ancient hex magic, huh?
Well, there is one place. My homeland, the Forest of Witches.
You think they'd help?
The Queen of the Witches' magic would.
Meanwhile, in the Forest of Witches...
Hey! The smartest witch ever to grace the land of witches has come back to say hello!
I have business here, so open up!
Open up!
."
Can you brave enough of the gym?
Yes.
This is graceful.
If I ever live everywhere what I can do,
何故私はここにいるの?
期待通りなどごめんなの
自分でやれるからさ
どうだっていい理屈ばっか
張り付いた
有りもっての世界を生きてく
誰かのためじゃない
今はまだ自分に追いつくまで
かむしゃらでじめき飛ばした
身体中の声が
翼切り抜けて
どんな未来も舞うよ
かぜうきて
自分を追い越すまで
ここで
It's women only? At last, I found my utopia!
I said they're witches, remember?
Yeah, so?
I've heard tell. Men who get too close have been turned to bugs and drowned in toilets.
Hold on. If they're witches...
Oh, right. When Vanessa disappeared out of nowhere, maybe she was going to ask their queen to fix Asta's arms.
The thing is, there's a strict rule that witches must live in the forest and nowhere else.
Which means that women like Vanessa and myself, who decided to leave, are looked upon as fugitives.
Your fugitives?
So she would need incredible resolve to go back there.
As for me, I'd fallen head over heels in love with my darling, so I had no choice in the matter!
That's true, honey bear. Both of us dove head first into a bottomless swamp of pure devotion.
Oh, Zell, I love you!
And I love you, Domina.
Good grief.
They're so in love, I'm jealous!
And after I gave up everything for you, I'm still living in this damn hovel, you worthless dead bitch!
What? No! What?
She always aims for his vital friends. Maybe she should have been the assassin.
Okay...
You know what? True love's overrated anyway.
Now what were we talking about?
Right, we should get back to business.
Yeah.
If Vanessa really did go back to those woods, I'm worried.
I don't know all of the details, but the rumors say that Vanessa was of special importance to the Queen of the Witches.
One thing's for certain though, once she goes in, it's going to be impossible for her to escape again.
The Queen is more deadly than you can imagine. So much so that the Diamond Kingdom won't even try to stand against her. And there's no hope of reasoning with her either.
So if you're planning to enter the Forest of Witches, it's only right of me to warn you. Angering the Queen will destroy any chance you had of returning with your lives.
We're going. Whatever it takes for us to heal Asta's arms.
She's right.
Domina, please tell us where it is.
I'm going with you.
Huh?
But you just said that...
Count me in too. I'm not letting anyone lay a finger on my sweet fiance.
Asta helped me out a lot when we first met and showed me what I needed to do to move forward. So I owe him, big time.
I don't like the idea of growing our debt either. Let's repay it.
Yeah. And besides all that, I could never live with myself if I left my last student out to dry.
If I can't use my arms, I'll just work on my lower body till it's perfect! I'm not gonna stop jumping!
I want super buff legs like this!
I got a crib!
Long time no see, Asta.
Whoa, it's old man Zell.
Hold on! Where the heck are you taking me?!
Let's go, we can explain on the way.
If we tell him.
There's no way I could let you guys go somewhere that dangerous for me!
He'll probably have a fit, so we'll just keep it a mystery for now.
Okay, we're off to the forest of W!
Wait, what's the W mean?
Please tell me it's for wonderful!
Problem solved.
Good job, Zell!
Very wise, Master. When I need to silence someone, all I can think of to do is kill them.
Uh, maybe you better work on that.
We should hurry up!
The other day there was this creepy guy outside the forest. He was staring at me and going, ha ha, over and over.
Wow, seriously? That's totally gross!
Oh, and by the way, I'm pretty sure I saw Vanessa around here not long ago.
What?! You're kidding!
If the Queen finds out she's here after what she did, I don't even want to think about what's going to happen to her.
Imperfect.
And I don't just mean you, Vanessa.
It's also true that my plans failed to reach perfection after you so selfishly fled from the forest of witches.
If you had mastered your thread magic the way I instructed you, you could have gained control over destiny itself.
But no, you let that man tempt you away instead.
Simply appalling.
To abandon your own people for an ordinary human male?
We are perfect witches with unlimited potential.
And you let him use you.
You should be ashamed!
You're ashamed!
oh dear what an imperfect room you're the one who's imperfect here's the deal
I'll come back to the forest on one condition teach me to dispel ancient
hexes or never see me again it appears you don't know your place so I'll show
you now the forest of witches there's witches here wait what could somebody
fill me in if you try to keep your voice down we have to be extremely careful
that's it now I'm worried why is everybody all quiet and serious is this
like a secret spy mission I'll tell you later we're about to bust in there's
only so much later it can get before it's too late look Asta if you don't hurry up
and shut your mouth shut it for you now what were you saying Domina the Queen's
used her tremendous magic power to cordon off this entire forest so if we cast
even a small spell she'll immediately know that we're here sounds like my
spatial magic won't do us a whole lot of good then she'll find us even if you
don't use it as soon as anyone with magic goes inside the forest the Queen will be
alerted if she spots us that means we'll be full of holes I don't have any magic so
good that all makes sense but how are we gonna get in luckily I have just the
invention I call this one's a vanish all just throw this on and poof your body
magic and presence will disappear in a flash that's marvelous I'm sure it's
expensive though of course not you can take one home for just 30,000 you'll
really wow what a great price but wait there's more by now and you'll get
another van a shawl absolutely free
D O M I N A just for you I've got everything you wanted at a bargain too
is this enough money and then some I'm kidding dear I'll let you use them for
free you say that now but everyone saw you think about taking her money I'm sure
she was just a bit startled by how much it was anyway look I think I see another
way in over there we should try it cute girl paradise here we come I still don't
know what's up be quiet
humans are so despicable they do nothing but hurt us and take things from us
mistress fauna the black bulls we're watching it appears they're up to
something strange I'll burn them to ashes I'm never going to forgive them for
killing Veto and for what they did to Lict
they'll pay for it they'll all pay
last time I went to the city I got approached out of nowhere by this creepy guy who kept saying ha ha and then he handed me a bouquet of a hundred roses
that's so weird
this is kind of crowded I could kill someone right now my apologies you two the
vanish all's were originally designed to cover one person but hey better than
getting shot at till we look like human honeycombs I guess we'll just have to
deal with it till we make it to the Queen at least we're fairing better than
they are I'm sorry we gotta get a lot close and personal guys apparently she
only made two of these things man this place is crawling with gorgeous magical
hotties and here I am stuck in a dude sandwich don't you think after all this I
deserve to know what the heck we're doing here are you sure you can't sell
this love potion for a little cheaper sorry I can't that almost sounded like a
man yelling you're imagining things there's no way a man could get into this
forest I guess not that was close sorry I couldn't help myself I've only ever seen
love potions in my wildest of dreams hey what's that thing it's weird but it's
kind of cute that's a security golem they may look harmless but the second they
detect an intruder they start swarming and firing off magical bullets now I
understand why you said that about honeycombs right if we let even one of
those things find out we're here they'll come fill us full of holes till we drop
dead a harmless-looking facade and a merciless attack they're the ideal
assassins here it comes don't worry if we're under the vanish all that can't see
us
okay it's our turn now
whoopsie are you kidding me
darling beautiful day isn't it what a nice place you got here
darling
you've done it now
you are way too naked to be this close to me
you what are you grabbing us for
he's a degenerate just the kind of thing my master's into
can't help yourself can you no that's not it
don't look at me like that hey what's going on
huh intruders male intruders it looks like all we can do now is try to blast our way
through to the queen's palace leave it to me I can use my spatial magic to make an
instant shortcut
hi there
hey this is no time to socialize
it's a naked old man
let's grab a coffee
cut it out finral
put it out finral
ah
creeper
hope to hear from you
take a hint would you
that's it grandpa
time to go
worst part is that wasn't a shortcut
no the worst part is how bad they shut me down
I'm still in shock here I don't know what the worst part is
crap we're surrounded
they use spew smoke I should have guessed it
spew smoke what's that
a special item that casts a smoke screen with trace amounts of magic
it'll clear out soon though
this is our chance to head straight to where the queen is
over there
man they should patch that
this way we can fly right in
I should have kept my shirt on so I wouldn't scrape up my bag
couldn't resist your urges shameful
it was an accident mario I swear an accident
that hurt
imperfect
she's got Vanessa
Vanessa
what do you think you're doing
I don't care if you are the queen or whatever
get your foot off our friend right now
you dare barge into my home and address me that way
perhaps you aren't aware of this
I'm the all-powerful queen of this forest and the mother of every witch here
some of you recognize me a friend there as well as little Vanessa are my descendants
I have more daughters than you could ever count and children need to be disciplined
what do you mean
this is a private family matter
you ought to mind your own business
I'm free to treat my children in any way I see fit
I don't know what's going on but it seems like you're the boss here
and you may be their mom or whatever
you're right I don't have any powers and now I guess I can't even fight you in my swords
but still unlike you I'd never step on my own family you must be that upstart
Vanessa talked about I honestly don't understand why she'd bother trying to repair trash like you
that's bizarre
do you not have any magic?
what a pitiful imperfect little brat you are
you're right I don't have any powers and now I guess I can't even fight you in my swords
but still unlike you I'd never step on my own family
I honestly don't understand why she'd bother trying to repair trash like you
she sacrificed everything
what a foolish girl I've raised
she told me she would become my slave and live out the rest of her days here
all for restoring those silly arms of yours
she really did that?
we're here for me?
when we first met you told me about the dream you had
you still have to become the wizard king right?
let us help once you have people who care about you
none of your problems or decisions you make are solely your own anymore
that is what you said isn't it Noelle?
of course
you guys
and on that note
that's impressive
I was hiding my intent to strike
however
old man you saved me
indeed
all I needed to do was create a diversion while the old man was rescuing Asta
yeah yeah
the old man did real good
now stop calling me that
here goes
win creation magic
emperor of slashing wins
take your foot off of her
she's one of us
so leave her alone
pitiful fools
what could such imperfect creatures possibly hope to do for her?
Vanessa
much like you all
is powerless to escape her destiny
this divination paints a lovely picture of the end that awaits you in mere moments
I didn't expect it to happen so soon
I knew they'd be coming
but now of all times
then again of course they'd choose a moment like this
the eye of the midnight sun
Zzzz
is
a
There won't be the magic they should give up
I was紅 if I'm breaking my glass
I'm rational
With awesome
I mean
I sellisti
I'll see you next time.
The Forest of G!
Ha ha! You've got to love the Magic Shopping Network.
What a bargain.
This amazing vanish-all can make you and your magic disappear.
It cost five million yule, but I'll have it paid off in 12 years.
Now I can enter that perfect oasis of beautiful women they call the Forest of Witches.
Ha ha!
But this is always the hardest part.
I know it's around here somewhere, but I'm not sure which way I need to go.
Something wrong.
Ha ha!
Who's there?
Let's be friends.
Ha ha!
Show yourself now!
You're scaring me.
I'm Gordon.
I'm Gordon, too.
What's good?
I'm Gordon.
I'm Gordon, dear.
I'm so glad you're my friend.
What?
But why?
Ah!
It's the Forest of Gordons!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun just launched an attack on the Forest of Witches.
Oh, and it looks like they're not the only ones.
Black Clover, page 58.
The Battlefield Decision.
And yes, my master's magic is taking his clothes off.